[
  
    {
      "question": "Who has written the story 'The Naive Friends'?",
      "choice1": "Prem Chand",
      "choice2": "Ray Douglas Bradbury",
      "choice3": "Zai Whitaker",
      "choice4": "Anita Desai",
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": " Why did Shyama keep quit in front of mother?",
      "choice1": "She was bold",
      "choice2": "She was weak",
      "choice3": "She was tense",
      "choice4": "She was scared",
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "What made Keshav and his sister forget about the joys of milk and jalebi?",
      "choice1": "The pleasure of seeing the flying of two birds.",
      "choice2": "The pleasure of reading books.",
      "choice3": "The pleasure of watching cinema.",
      "choice4": "None of these",
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question":"What did the children do to protect the eggs in the story 'The Naive Friends'?",
      "choice1": "made nest and cover",
      "choice2": "made cage and cornice",
      "choice3": "made cushion and roof",
      "choice4": "made clothes and cover",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Where did the birds lay their eggs in the story 'The Naive Friends'?",
      "choice1": "above the roof",
      "choice2":"above the cornice",
      "choice3":"above the window",
      "choice4": "above the garage",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question":"How did Keshav manage to reach the cornice?",
      "choice1":"by climbing on stool", 
      "choice2": "by climbing on rope",
      "choice3": "by climbing on ladder ",
      "choice4": "None of these",
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Why did the birds drop the eggs themselves?", 
      "choice1": "The nest was broken",
      "choice2": "They were tainted",
      "choice3": "the chicks had come out",
      "choice4": "They were very small",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question":"A bird had laid eggs ....... the cornice.", 
      "choice1":"just below", 
      "choice2": "near",
      "choice3": "just above",
      "choice4":"None of these",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question":"Who has written the story 'Kali and the Rat Snake'?",
      "choice1": "Prem Chand",
      "choice2": "Ray Douglas Bradbury",
      "choice3": "Zai Whitaker",
      "choice4": "Anita Desai",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question":"Kali belongs to which tribe?", 
      "choice1": "Irula tribe",
      "choice2": "Khasi tribe",
      "choice3":"Munda tribe",
      "choice4":"Paharia tribe",
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question":"Who was sitting on the desk in the story 'Kali and the Rat Snake'?",
      "choice1": "Teacher",
      "choice2":"Kali",
      "choice3":"Rat Snake",
      "choice4":"Ramesh",
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question":"What had Kali brought for lunch?", 
      "choice1": "bread",
      "choice2": "termites",
      "choice3":"chapati",
      "choice4":"snacks",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question":"Why did Kali hate going to school?", 
      "choice1": "he liked to play at home",
      "choice2": "it was very far",
      "choice3": "he had no friends",
      "choice4": "the teachers disliked him",
      "answer": 3
    },
   
  {
    "question": "Why were the Children in the class shouting for help?",
    "choice1": "because they saw fire",
    "choice2":"because they saw a tiger",
    "choice3":"because they saw a rat snake",
    "choice4": "None of these",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question":"Who belonged to Kanathoor village?", 
    "choice1": "Kali",
    "choice2": "Keshav",
    "choice3":"Praksha",
    "choice4": "Repesh",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question":"What does WCF stand for?",
    "choice1": "West Cooling Factor",
    "choice2": "Wind Chill Factor",
    "choice3": "Wind Cooling Factor",
    "choice4": "None of these",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
      "question":"What does the word 'Siachen' really mean?",
      "choice1":"A land with an abundance of snow",
      "choice2":"A land with an abundance of grasses",
      "choice3":"A land with an abundance of sheep",
      "choice4":"A land with an abudance of roses",
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the leading cause of deaths in siachen ?",
      "choice1": "Poor clothing and WCF",
      "choice2": "Strong winds and no electricity",
      "choice3": "Avalanche and other environmental factors",
      "choice4":"Disease and envvironmental factors", 
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Name 'Siachen' refers to a land with an abundance of --", 
      "choice1": "Ice",
      "choice2": "Water",
      "choice3": "Roses",
      "choice4":"Rock",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question":"What miracle did the Emperor's servant see?", 
      "choice1":"A man ploughing in the field",
      "choice2": "A man flying in the sky",
      "choice3": "A man constructing a house",
      "choice4": "A man playing football",
      "answer": 2
    }
    
   
]